{
    "id": "f0fb65ce2aa6450a935e3a3d35d24b1a",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is quite proud ………………………. her legacy.",
            "description": "Proud is followed by of. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ………………………….. on the exam.",
            "description": "Use of + ing form after accused. ",
            "answers": [
                "to cheat",
                "of cheating",
                "with cheating"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He accused me of …………………………….. to him.",
            "description": "Write of + ing form after accused. ",
            "answers": [
                "lying",
                "laying",
                "lie"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The headmaster congratulated the boy …………………………… his success.",
            "description": "Either on or for is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team is very confident …………………………… the match.",
            "description": "Write of + ing form after confident. ",
            "answers": [
                "to win",
                "of winning",
                "for winning"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was acquitted …………………………… the charges levelled against him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ……………………………… tired to walk.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too...to...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. the bell rang, the students rushed out.",
            "description": "As soon as is used to indicate that one thing happens immediately after another.",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                "As long as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Unless he …………………………. smoking, his health will not improve.",
            "description": "Use a simple present tense in the unless clause and simple future in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "quits",
                "quitted",
                "has quitted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were rich, I ………………………………. to charities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will donate",
                "would donate",
                "would have donated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This news is too good ………………………………… true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to be",
                "that it cannot be"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is too clever ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to cheat",
                "to be cheated",
                "that he cannot be cheated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}